A Finding Aid to the Frank K. M. Rehn Galleries Records, 1858-1969 (bulk 1919-1968), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, A-Z, 1858-1969; undated; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 1-15; 14.4 linear feet; Reels 5849-5869)
  - United Federation of Postal Clerks - United States War Production Board, 1919-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 1243-1334)
    United States Foreign Service
    United States House of Representatives, Ways and Means Committee
    United States National Museum (See Smithsonian Institution)
    United States Office of War Information
    United States Treasury Department
    United States War Department
    United States War Production Board
  - University Club - University of Georgia, 1941-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 1335-1428)
    University Club
    University of Arizona
    University of California, Los Angeles
    University of Georgia
  - University of Illinois - University of Kentucky, 1947-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 1429-1515)
    University of Illinois, Krannert Art Museum
    University of Kansas
    University of Kentucky
  - University of Maine - University of Montana, 1940-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Reel 5866, Frame 1516-1597)
    University of Maine
    University of Manitoba
    University of Maryland
    University of Miami, Joe and Emily Lowe Art Gallery
    University of Michigan
    University of Minnesota, Duluth
    University of Minnesota, Minneapolis
    University of Missouri
    University of Montana
  - University of Nebraska, 1940-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Reel 5867, Frame 12-133)
  - University of New Mexico - Vander Poel, 1922-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Reel 5867, Frame 134-231)
    University of New Mexico
    University of North Carolina
    University of Oklahoma
    University of Oregon
    University of Pennsylvania
    University of Pittsburgh
    University of South Carolina
    University of Southern California
    University of Texas
    University of Utah
    University of Vermont
    University of Virginia
    University of Washington
    University of Wisconsin, Elvehjm Art Center
    University of Wyoming
    University Press
    University Prints
    Upjohn Company
    Uplinger, Mrs. J. E.
    Upton, D. F.
    Urig, Russel
    Urquhart,Tony
    Usui, Bumpei
    Utica Public Library
    Utley, Gordon D.
    Vachon, Andrew William
    Vahinger, Fred
    Alfred Valente Gallery
    Valparaiso University, Sloan Galleries of American Paintings
    Van Buren, Jessica T.
    Van Evera, Caroline
    E. H. Van Ingen and Co.
    Van Pelt, Andrew
    Van Veen, S.
    Vander Poel, H. B.
  - Verle Gallery - Virges, 1920-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Reel 5867, Frame 232-292)
    Verle Gallery
    Verleger, F. Kind
    Vermont, Louise
    Vezin, Charles
    Vidor, King
    James Vigeveno Galleries
    Vincent, Fred C.
    Vincent, Harry A.
    Virges, E. M., II
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1939-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Reel 5867, Frame 293-434)
  - Vitale - Von Stein, 1924-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 436-453)
    Vitale, Ferruccio
    Vivino, Elmer
    Vogue
    Volz, Harry A.
    von Keller, Beatrice
    Von Stein, William G.
  - R. C. and N. A. Vose/Robert C. Vose Galleries, 1919-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 454-552)
  - Voth - Wade, 1924-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 553-560)
    Voth, Harold M.
    B. B. Wachtel Insurance
    Waddington Galleries, Inc.
    Wade, J. H.
  - Wadsworth Athenaeum, 1927-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 561-683)
  - Wadsworth, Isabella - Walden School, 1918-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 684-712)
    Wadsworth, Isabella
    Wager, Stella
    Wagman, Evelyn L.
    Wagner, Richard E.
    Wakefield-Young Books
    Walbridge, Norton S.
    Wald, J. S.
    Waldburger, Ernest R. S.
    Walden School
  - Walker Art Center, 1943-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 713-798)
  - Walker, Edith - Warner, Keith, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 799-905)
    Walker, Edith
    Walker Galleries/Maynard Walker/Collectors' Finds
    Walker, Harrington F.
    Walker, Mrs. Hudson D.
    Walker, Joseph
    Walker, Maynard (See Walker Galleries)
    Walker, Robert N.
    Walker, Stewart
    Walker, Wes
    Wallace, A. B.
    Wallace, Mrs. G. S.
    Wallace, Josephine
    Wallace, McClelland
    Wallenstein, Alfred
    Waller, B. G.
    Wallingford, Gertrude
    Wallingford, Katrina
    Walsh, Henry
    Walsh, John R.
    Walsh, W.
    Walter, Mrs. W. G.
    Walters, Emile
    Walther League Messenger
    Walton, Joseph E.
    Wands, Alfred
    Warburg, Mrs. Gerald
    Warburg, James P.
    Warner, George B.
    Warner, George C.
    Warner, H. L.
    Warner, Keith
  - Warner, Ruth, 1939-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 906-998)
  - Warrell - Watherston, 1927-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 999-1031)
    Warrell, Richard
    Warren, Mrs. H. E.
    Warren, Whitney
    Washburn, Mrs. Gordon
    Washburn, Ives
    Washington County Museum of Fine Arts
    Washington Irving Gallery
    Washington University
    Wasserman, Burt
    Wasson, Mrs. William A.
    Watercolor Gallery
    Waters, Sylvia
    Watherston, Margaret M.
  - Watkins, Franklin C. and Ida, 1939-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 1032-1243)
  - Watkins, P. - Winefried, 1918-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5867, Frame 1244-1553)
    Watkins, Franklin C. and Ida
    Watkins, Paul
    Watson, Forbes and Nan
    Watson, Penn R., Jr.
    Watt, S. W.
    Waugh, Colton
    Waugh, Grace W.
    Webb, E. T.
    Webber, Eloise
    Webber, John C.
    Weber, Bill, Jr.
    Weber, E. A.
    Weber, Mosley
    Weber, Mrs. Orlando
    Webster, Hutton, Jr.
    Wechsler, Mrs. Walter M.
    Weed, Bertha A.
    Weeks, Carl
    Weidner, Roswell
    Weinberger, Harry
    Weingarten, Victor
    Weir, Ella Baker (Mrs. J. Alden)
    Weiss, Belle
    Weiss, George
    Weiss, Winefride J.
  - Weid - E. Weyhe Gallery, 1927-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5868, Frame 12-95)
    Weid, F. M.
    Welles, Orson
    Wellesley College
    Wellington, Gertrude
    Wells, Charles E.
    Wells College
    Wells, Fred N.
    Wending, Erwin
    Wengler, Harold
    Wenner, Robert B.
    Anna L. Werbe Galleries
    Wesleyan University, Davison Art Center
    West Valley Tea Room
    Western Association of Art Museum Directors
    Westheimer, Jerome
    Westminster Hotel
    Westover School
    Wetsman, Janis B.
    Wexler, George
    E. Weyhe Gallery
  - WGBH Television - Whitney, Mrs. John Hay, 1919-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5868, Frame 96-157)
    WGBH Television
    Wheaton College
    Wheeler, Charles V.
    Wheeler, Steve
    Wheelwright, Robert
    Whelan, Gloria
    Whimpfheimer, Charles A.
    Whitcomb, John M.
    White, Mr.
    White, A. M.
    White and Quinn
    White, F.
    White, Helen
    White, Jane
    White, John F.
    L. F. White Co.
    White, Marion
    White, Meade Fitzhugh, II
    White, Paul
    White, Mrs. Robert H.
    William A. White and Sons
    Whitehead, Jane Byrd Radcliffe
    Whitehead Productions
    Whitehead, Robert
    Whiteley, James Gustavus
    Whitney, Arthur
    Whitney, Cornelius Vanderbilt
    Whitney, Mrs. John Hay
  - Whitney Museum of American Art (includes Friends of the Whitney Museum of American Art), 1939-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5868, Frame 158-603)
  - Whitney Studio Club - Wills, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5868, Frame 604-701)
    Whitney Studio Club
    Whittier, Ross
    Whittington, Eugene
    Wichita Art Association
    Wick, Philip
    Wiegand, Gustav
    Wierke, Conrad
    Wisenberg, Mrs. Louis
    Wiggins, Guy C.
    Wigglesworth, Frank
    Wildenstein and Co., Inc.
    Wilder, Ruth
    Wilk, Mrs. Max
    Wilkinson, Edward A.
    Williams, Charles F.
    Williams College, Lawrence Art Museum
    Williams, E. A.
    Williams, Edgar
    Williams, H. A.
    Williams, Hiram
    Williams, Mrs. Lawrence A.
    Williams, Oliver
    Williams, Wayne F.
    Williard, Robert P.
    Willimantic State College
    Willis, Betty
    Willis, Mrs. Frederic A.
    Wills, Mrs. W. G.
  - Wilmington Society of the Fine Arts - Winnipeg Art Gallery Association, 1926-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5868, Frame 702-749)
    Wilmington Society of the Fine Arts
    Wilson Auto Repair Shop
    Wilson, Edwin Carleton
    Wilson, Ralph L.
    Wing, Barbara D.
    Wing, James G.
    Wingate, Arline
    Winnipeg Art Gallery Association
  - Winters, Denny, 1947-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Reel 5868, Frame 750-1034)
  - Winters, Helen C. - Woodstock Artists Association, 1920-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Reel 5868, Frame 1036-1125)
    Winters, Helen C.
    Winton, Flora and Frank J.
    Wise, Howard E.
    Wislocki, George B.
    Witherspoon, Mary Eleanor
    Witte, Edward H., Jr.
    Witte Memorial Museum/San Antonio Art League
    Witter, Faith A.
    Wolf, Ben and Ruth
    Wolf, Stanley J.
    Wolfe, William D.
    Wolfert, Helen
    Wolpin, Kay
    Woman's Day Magazine
    Woman's Home Companion
    Women's American ORT
    Women's Club
    Wood, Franklin S.
    Wood, Charles Erskine Scott
    Wood, Robert W., Jr.
    Ruby Ross Wood, Inc.
    Woodhouse, Betty Burroughs (See also Burroughs, Betty)
    Woodin, Mrs. William H.
    Woodmere Art Gallery
    Woodruff, Adele G.
    Woodstock Artists Association
  - Woodward - Wootton, 1922-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Reel 5868, Frame 1126-1183)
    Woodward, George
    Woodward, Ruth M.
    Wootton, Ruby Smith
  - Worcester Art Museum, 1924-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Reel 5868, Frame 1184-1294)
  - Workman - Wylie, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Reel 5868, Frame 1295-1414)
    Workman, David T.
    World
    World Book Encyclopedia
    World Collectors Annuary
    World Journal Tribune, Inc.
    Worldwide Press, Inc.
    Worringer, Anne
    Worth Avenue Gallery
    Wose, Frederick
    Wray, Mrs. George D., Jr.
    Wrenn, Helen B. (mother of Peggy W. Rehn)
    Wrenn, Mr. and Mrs. Harold H.
    WRFM Radio
    Wright, Clifford
    Wright, H. P.
    Wright, Norman Bartlett
    Wulp, John
    Wyer's Refrigeration
    Wyeth, Andrew
    Wyeth, John C.
    Wylie, Adele M.
  - Yaddo - Yunt Art Galleries, 1919-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Reel 5868, Frame 1416-1517)
    Yaddo
    Yale University
    Yale University Art Gallery
    Yamet Arts, Inc.
    Yancey, S. foster
    Yandik, Charles
    Yasinow, J. B.
    Year
    YMCA/YWCA, Ashtabula, Ohio
    YWCA, Fredericksburg, Va.
    YMHA/YWHA, Essex Co., N.J.
    Yocom, Mrs. P.C.
    Yonkers Museum of Science and Arts
    Yorke, Oswald
    Young, E. C.
    Young, Elaine
    Howard Young Galleries
    Young, J. W.
    Young, Katherine
    Young, Mahonri
    Young Stark
    Young, Susan F.
    Young, Mrs. Thomas F.
    Young, William
    Younger, Helen Walcott
    Youngman, William H.
    Youth Today
    Yunt Art Galleries
  - Zabriskie Gallery - Zsissly, 1939-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Reel 5869, Frame 13-61)
    Zabriskie Gallery
    Zacharias, Jean
    Zaus, Earl A.
    Zegarelli, Dr.
    Zeltzerman, M.
    Zeirler, William S.
    Zierner, Thelma
    Zinn
    Zinsser, J. S.
    Zinsser, William H.
    Zion, A.
    Zipin, M.
    Zorach, William
    Zorne, Mrs. A. E.
    Zsissly
  - Zucker - Zunser, 1953-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Reel 5869, Frame 62-159)
    Zucker, Harry T./Zucker, Weiden and Shapiro
    R. M. Zucker and Company
    Zunser, Shomer
  - Unknown and Illegible, 1922-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Reel 5869, Frame 161-271)
  - Stenographer's Notebook (outgoing letters in shorthand), 1947-January 31, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Reel 5869, Frame 273-374)
- Financial Records, 1919-1968; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 15-17; 2.6 linear feet; Reel 5869)
  Of particular interest are monthly insurance schedules indicating painting titles and values, and specifying additions and deletions from the previous month. The remaining insurance records have not been microfilmed.
  Investment records, filed by names of investment firms, relate to numerous personal and business accounts, including estates of Rehn family members.
  Miscellaneous financial records include a file relating to the estate of Frank Rehn's first wife, Peggy W. Rehn, and gallery inventories. Two volumes of receipts record incoming paintings; similar loose receipts are with Series 1. Paid bills are for routine business expenses and some personal expenses; the art-related purchases documented here are framing and painting conservation. Receipts for paintings bought by the gallery are with Series 1.
  Arrangement note
  This series is arranged into 6 subseries:
  2.1: Banking, 1920-1968
  2.2: Insurance, 1920-1968
  2.3: Investments, 1919-1968, undated
  2.4: Taxes, 1916-1964, undated
  2.5: Miscellaneous Financial Records, 1937-1951, undated
  2.6: Paid Bills, 1919-1969
  - Banking, 1920-1968; 2.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Bank for Savings (Margaret S. Rehn), 1929-1934; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Bank of New York (Frank K. M. Rehn, Inc.), 1967-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Bankers Trust Company (John J. Clancy and J. J. Clancy Special), 1953-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Chase National Bank (Margaret S. Rehn), 1946-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Chemical Bank and Trust Company (Frank K. M. Rehn), 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - East River Savings Bank (John J. Clancy), 1959-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Empire Trust Company (Frank K. M. Rehn, Inc.), 1933-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Empire Trust Company (Frank K. M. Rehn), 1919-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Empire Trust Company (Frank K. M. Rehn Special), 1941-1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Empire Trust Company (Estate of Frank K. M. Rehn), 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Empire Trust Company (Estate of Peggy W. Rehn), 1942-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Manchester Trust Company, 1942-1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Loans (Frank K. M. Rehn and John J. Clancy), 1920-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Safe Deposit Rental Receipts (Frank K. M. Rehn, Peggy W. Rehn, and John J. Clancy), 1919-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
  - Insurance, 1920-1968; 2.2; Archival Resource Key
    - Insurance Policies, 1920-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Insurance Policies, 1923-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Insurance Schedules, 1922-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Reel 5869, Frame 380-792)
  - Investments, 1919-1968; 2.3; Archival Resource Key
    - H. L. Allen and Company, 1923; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Dreyfus Fund, Incorporated, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Hemphill, Noyes and Co./Hemphill, Noyes, Graham, Parsons and Co., 1942-1964; undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Jesup and Lamont, 1927; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Lee, Higginson and Company, 1922-1925; undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1919-1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
  - Taxes, 1916-1964; 2.4; Archival Resource Key
    - Federal, 1918-1949; 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Payroll, 1950-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - New York State, 1920-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Gloucester, Mass., 1916-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - Englewood Cliffs, N. J., 1940-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
    - New York, N. Y., 1919-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Records, 1937-1951; undated; 2.5; Archival Resource Key
    - Estate of Peggy W. Rehn, 1942-1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 16)
    - Inventories of Gallery Stock (includes consignments and frames), circa 1919-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Reel 5869, Frame 798-878)
    - Notes regarding Business Expenses and Income, 1919-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Reel 5869, Frame 880-1185)
    - Receipts for Incoming Paintings, 1937-1939; 1946-1948; Archival Resource Key; (2 vols.) (Box 16, Reel 5869, Frame 1189-1331)
  - Paid Bills, 1919-1969; 2.6; Archival Resource Key
    - A - Z, 1918-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 16)
    - A - Z, 1951-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17)
- Scrapbooks, 1919-1940; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 23-24; 0.6 linear feet; Reels 5869-5870)
  This series contains five volumes documenting the activities of Rehn Galleries and its associated artists, 1919, 1923-1941, that contain clippings and a small number of exhibition catalogs. An autographed photograph of Walter Griffin is in volume 1. Items on former reel NY59/17 (frames 165-293) were missing from volume 1 when inspected in October 1981. This material was thought to have been returned to the donor after microfilming, and reader-printer copies were inserted as substitutes in 1981. In 2003, these items were found and are now interfiled with the appropriate series (correspondence, printed matter, works of art, and miscellaneous items).
  - Vol. 1:, 1919; 1923-1928; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Reel 5869, Frame 1337-1421)
  - Vol. 2:, 1928-1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Reel 5869, Frame 1423-1696)
  - Vol. 3:, 1930-1933; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Reel 5870, Frame 13-132)
  - Vol. 4:, 1934-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Reel 5870, Frame 134-201)
  - Vol. 5:, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Reel 5870, Frame 203-261)
- Printed Matter, 1882-1969; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 18-20; 2.5 linear feet; Reels 5870-5872)
  Printed matter relating to Rehn Galleries consists of items about the gallery, as well as publications produced by Rehn Galleries. Included are feature articles, exhibition reviews, announcements and catalogs of artists affiliated with the gallery. Also found here are exhibition catalogs, press releases, and invitations produced by the gallery. General, art-related printed matter consists of articles, auction catalogs, advertisements, and publications of various museums, arts organizations, and schools; also included are feature articles, exhibition reviews, announcements, and catalogs of artists not affiliated with Rehn Galleries. Additional printed items concern miscellaneous subjects that are not art-related.
  This series is arranged into 3 subseries:
  4.1: Rehn Galleries, 1919-1969, undated
  4.2: General, Art-Related, 1882-1968, undated
  4.3: Miscellaneous Subjects, Not Art-Related, 1910-1967, undated
  - Rehn Galleries, 1919-1969; 4.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Rehn Galleries Advertisements, 1925-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 266-299)
    - Rehn Artists, A - Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5870)
      - Bacon - Botkin, 1918-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 301-347)
      - Brook - Brown, 1940-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 348-389)
      - Burchfield, Charles E., 1935-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 390-556)
      - Campanella - Fiene, 1930-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 557-608)
      - Gikow - Hite, 1921-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 609-673)
      - Hopper, Edward, 1934-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 674-756)
      - Hubbard - Kaufman, 1942-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 757-831)
      - Kimball - Kroll, 1932-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 832-900)
      - Lathrop - Mangravite, 1920-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 901-970)
      - Marsh, Reginald, 1934-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 971-1052)
      - Mattson - Powers, 1920-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5870, Frame 1053-1154)
      - Raffo - Schwieder, 1933-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5871, Frame 13-50)
      - Sparhawk-Jones - Spruance, 1932-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5871, Frame 51-94)
      - Strater, Henry, 1961-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5871, Frame 95-175)
      - Tomlin - Twachtman, 1921-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5871, Frame 176-231)
      - Watkins - Young, 1922-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5871, Frame 232-287)
    - Rehn Artists, Group Shows, 1920-1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Reel 5871, Frame 289-532)
    - Rehn Artists, Group Shows, 1945-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Reel 5871, Frame 535-1021)
    - Rehn Galleries Exhibition Catalogs, Press Releases, Invitations, 1920-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Reel 5871, Frame 1023-1328)
    - Rehn Galleries Exhibition Catalogs, Press Releases, Invitations, cont., 1920-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Reel 5872, Frame 13-51)
    - Rehn Galleries Exhibition Catalogs, Press Releases, Invitations, 1920-1966; Archival Resource Key; (duplicates unfilmed) (Box 19)
  - General, Art-Related, 1882-1968; 4.2; Archival Resource Key
    - Advertisements for Frames and Supplies, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Articles about Art Collectors, 1928-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Articles about Art Sales and Prices, 1922-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Articles about Fakes and Forgeries, 1963-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Articles about Museums, 1949-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Articles about U.S. Exhibition in Moscow, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Articles about Miscellaneous Topics, 1921-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Artists (not Rehn), A-K, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 19)
    - Artists (not Rehn), L - Z, 1920-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 20)
    - Artists (not Rehn), Group Shows, 1931-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 20)
    - Auction Catalogs, 1882-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 20)
    - Book Prospectuses and Information about Periodical Subscriptions and Advertising, 1921-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 20)
    - Fuller Building Floor Plan, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20)
    - Publications, Art Schools, 1933-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 20)
    - Publications, Arts Organizations, A - Z, 1953-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 20)
    - Publications, Museums, A - Z, 1936-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous Subjects, Not Art-Related, 1910-1967; 4.3; Archival Resource Key
    - Miscellaneous, 1910-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 20)
- Miscellaneous Records, circa 1920-1968; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 20-21; 0.7 linear feet; Reel 5872)
  Artwork consists of undated painted Christmas cards by Yeffee Kimball and Denny Winters, and a painted greeting card by Warren Chappell sent to Reginald Marsh. Pen and ink drawings, 1925-1927 and undated, are by George Luks, Reginald Marsh, Mahonri Young, and unidentified artists. Other artwork includes a sketchbook and watercolor painting by Reginald Marsh.
  Among the writings are a short story, "The Power of Money," probably by Frank K. M. Rehn, poems by Coleman Kamile and unknown, and an unsigned essay titled "An American Collector."
  - Artwork, A-Z, 1925-1927; undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Reel 5872)
    - Chappell, Warren, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Reel 5872, Frame 55-56)
    - Kimball, Yeffee, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Reel 5872, Frame 57-58)
    - Luks, George, 1925; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Reel 5872, Frame 59-60)
    - Marsh, Reginald, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Reel 5872, Frame 61-70)
    - Winters, Denny, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Reel 5872, Frame 71-73)
    - Young, Mahonri, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Reel 5872, Frame 74-76)